Guide to the Yale Events and Activities Photographs
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Photographs of Mike Marsland, university photographer, documenting Yale University, 1977-2003; Accession 2009-A-070
  - Silliman, Benjamin: Yale's first professor of chemistry, Circa 1990s (Box 7, Folder 547)
  - Slifka Center Groundbreaking [mm and JA 275], 1993 May 30 (Box 7, Folder 548)
  - Simon, Paul: color prints and negatives, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 549)
  - Sloan Physics -- landscaping: Sterling Chemistry Laboratory [mm 84], 1993 December 14 (Box 7, Folder 550)
  - Cyd Slotoroff -- YalePsychiatric Institute [mm 134], 1993 April 1 (Box 7, Folder 551)
  - Smilow Field Center [mm 481], 1993 September 18 (Box 7, Folder 552)
  - Smilow Field Center -- Renovation [mm 108], 1993 May 10 (Box 7, Folder 553)
  - Smith, Anna Devere at Medical School, Circa 1990s (Box 7, Folder 554)
  - Snow shots, 2000-2001 (Box 7, Folder 555)
  - Soccer (Morse versus JE), 2000November (Box 7, Folder 556)
  - Social Science Library [mm 420], 1996 October (Box 7, Folder 557)
  - Society of Humanists, Atheists and Agnostics Friday, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 558)
  - Solar Car [mm 458], 1997 April 18 (Box 7, Folder 559)
  - Space Shuttle: Yale Banner and Droplet Experiment [mm 115], 1992 July 7 (Box 7, Folder 560)
  - Special Olympics
    - AYA panel [mm 224], 1994 August (Box 7, Folder 561)
    - Portrait, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 562)
    - [mm 152], 1994 May 13 (Box 7, Folder 563)
    - [mm 242], 1994 October (Box 7, Folder 564)
    - Equipment (donated PWG) [mm 315], 1995 March 29 (Box 7, Folder 565)
    - Grant [mm 63], 1993 November 30 (Box 7, Folder 566)
    - Signs -- Installation [mm 309], 1995 May 10 (Box 7, Folder 567)
    - News Conference [mm 269], 1995 March 9 (Box 7, Folder 568)
    - Press Conference [mm 320], 1995 June 12 (Box 7, Folder 569)
    - Preparation [mm 321], 1995 June (Box 7, Folder 570)
    - Global Auction [mm 267], 1995 March 9 (Box 7, Folder 571)
    - Training Session [mm 308], 1995 April 4 (Box 7, Folder 572)
    - Volunteers [mm 266], 1995 (Box 7, Folder 573)
    - Channel 3 [mm270], 1995 January 10 (Box 7, Folder 574)
  - Spider/Bethany Teachman, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 575)
  - Sports Camp, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 576)
  - Starr, Ken, Circa 1990s (Box 7, Folder 577)
  - George Stephanopolous [mm 262], 1995 February 18 (Box 7, Folder 578)
  - STEP/LEAP Programs [mm 80], 1993 August (Box 7, Folder 579)
  - Specialized Treatment Early in Psychosis (STEP) Program [mm 220], 1994 July 27 (Box 7, Folder 580)
  - Sterling Memorial Library
    - Windows [mm 381], 1996 May (Box 7, Folder 581)
    - Selin Courtyard Dedication, 1991 June 5 (Box 7, Folder 582)
    - Main Reference Room Dedication Starr Foundation, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 583)
    - Renovations [mm 410], 1996 (Box 7, Folder 584)
    - Elms + Magnolias Exhibit [mm 397], 1996 May (Box 7, Folder 585 - 586)
    - Long Service Awards [mm 365], 1995 September 29 (Box 7, Folder 587)
    - Memorabilia Room [mm 398], 1996 May (Box 7, Folder 588)
    - Windows, Circa 1990s (Box 7, Folder 589)
    - Sterling Scholars: Elm-Ivy, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 590)
  - Stewart, Martha [mm 376], 1996 April 10 (Box 7, Folder 591)
  - Stone Carvings, Circa 1990s (Box 7, Folder 592)
  - Stout, Susan (portrait), Circa 1990s (Box 7, Folder 593)
  - Student Computer Center [mm 434], 1996 September (Box 7, Folder 594)
  - Student Life: Baseball Caps [mm 135], 1992 November 24 (Box 7, Folder 595)
  - Students at Yale Daily News (Photos), 2000 (Box 7, Folder 596)
  - Styron, William: Master's Tea MTM, 2001 May (Box 7, Folder 597)
  - Subatomic Particle [mm 159], 1994 April 25 (Box 7, Folder 598)
  - Summer Sports Camp mm 396, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 599)
  - Summers, Larry, Circa 1990s (Box 7, Folder 600)
  - Surgeon General of the United States: Dr. David Satcher Visit, 1999 April 5-12 (Box 7, Folder 601)
  - Swing Dance class [mm 470.1], 1998 (Box 7, Folder 602)
  - Swing Dorm [mm 494], 1997 (Box 7, Folder 603)
  - TV Studio, 2001 January (Box 7, Folder 604)
  - Talking Heads/Richard Gans, Circa 1990s (Box 7, Folder 605)
  - Teacher's Institute -- National Advisory [mm 206], 1994 (Box 7, Folder 606)
  - "Team New Haven", Circa 1990s (Box 7, Folder 607)
  - Technology Access Center, Circa 1990s (Box 7, Folder 608)
  - Tercentennial Brochure [mm 471.1], 1998 (Box 7, Folder 609)
  - Tercentennial Brochure [Secretary's Office coordinators], 1999 (Box 7, Folder 610)
  - Tetelman Fellowship [mm 413], 1996 May (Box 7, Folder 611)
  - Theatre Play with Peter Salovey, Circa 1990s (Box 7, Folder 612)
  - Helen Thomas Poynter Tea, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 613)
  - Three (Musical) Sisters (Portrait) YBC, 2000 January 10 (Box 7, Folder 614)
  - Town Green Special Services District, juggler "Amazing Andy" (YBC), 1999 May 31-June 21 (Box 7, Folder 615)
  - Travel Office [mm 303], 1995 May 17 (Box 7, Folder 616)
  - Truman Scholars, 1996 October 2 (Box 7, Folder 617)
  - Truman Scholars, 2001 April 2 (Box 7, Folder 618 - 619)
  - Turkey Scenic [mm 316], 1994 November (Box 7, Folder 620)
  - Turow, Scott: Law Sch Lecture, 1999 February 18 (Box 7, Folder 621)
  - Tutoring Program [mm 289], 1995 March 27 (Box 7, Folder 622)
  - Archbishop Desmond Tutu [mm 260], 1994 October 7 (Box 7, Folder 623)
  - Tyler Prize [mm 95], 1994 April 11 (Box 7, Folder 624)
  - United Way
    - Kick-Off [mm 32], 1993 September 14 (Box 8, Folder 625)
    - Julia Denes at Leila Day Nursery [mm 55], 1993 September (Box 8, Folder 626)
    - Promo [mm 235], 1994 March 10 (Box 8, Folder 627)
    - Promo [mm 265], 1994 November 15 (Box 8, Folder 628)
    - Promo [mm 342], 1995 September (Box 8, Folder 629)
    - Ticket Winner [mm 282], 1995 March 8 (Box 8, Folder 630)
    - Promo-Q House [mm 273], 1994 December 6 (Box 8, Folder 631)
  - U.N. Delegates [mm 299], 1995 April 3 (Box 8, Folder 632)
  - Undergraduate Admissions, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 633)
  - Undergraduate Career Services [mm 439], 1996 September 13 (Box 8, Folder 634)
  - Union Contract Settlement [mm 430], 1996 December (Box 8, Folder 635)
  - United Way
    - [mm 200], 1994 July 28 (Box 8, Folder 636)
    - Blood Drive [mm 352], 1995 November 8 (Box 8, Folder 637)
    - Brochure cover [mm 325], 1995 August 16 (Box 8, Folder 638)
    - Campaign Promo [mm 433], 1996 September 17 (Box 8, Folder 639)
    - Campaign [mm 341], 1995 October 31 (Box 8, Folder 640)
    - Campaign [mm 109], 1992 September (Box 8, Folder 641)
    - Promo [mm 463], 1997 September 16 (Box 8, Folder 642)
  - USA TODAY All- USA College Academic Team Jillian Cutler Winner YBC, 1999 March 1-8 (Box 8, Folder 643 - 644)
  - Urban Affairs Conference [HS 14], 1993 January 23 (Box 8, Folder 645)
  - Veith Resource Center [mm 473], 1997 November 6 (Box 8, Folder 646)
  - Veteran's Day Ceremony, 1999 November (Box 8, Folder 647)
  - Video Conferencing [mm 344], 1996 January 10 (Box 8, Folder 648)
  - Visiting Faculty [mm 300], 1995 April 7 (Box 8, Folder 649)
  - Visitor Information Center [mm 310], 1995 May 8 (Box 8, Folder 650)
  - Lewis Walpole Library [mm 386], 1996 June 18 (Box 8, Folder 651)
  - Webmaster at Yale: Patrick Lynch [YBC], 1999 March 8-22 (Box 8, Folder 652)
  - Whiffenpoofs, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 653 - 656)
  - Whitney Grove Press conference [mm 480], 1997 October 15 (Box 8, Folder 657)
  - Whitney Humanities Center conference [mm 345], 1995 October (Box 8, Folder 658)
  - Wilbur Cross Medals, Spring 1998 (Box 8, Folder 659)
  - Wilbur Cross Medal [mm 286], 1994 May 23 (Box 8, Folder 660)
  - Robin Winks -- Seminar [mm 110], 1992 February 25 (Box 8, Folder 661)
  - W.I.S.E. Program [mm 421], 1996 October 17 (Box 8, Folder 662)
  - Woodcarving [mm 460], 1997 April (Box 8, Folder 663)
  - Women's Campaign School
    - [mm 210], 1994 June 3 (Box 8, Folder 664)
    - [mm 323], 1995 June 1 (Box 8, Folder 665)
    - [mm 387], 1996 June 5-9 (Box 8, Folder 666)
  - Women's Table Installation [mm 41], 1993 August 24 (Box 8, Folder 667)
  - Women's Table [mm 49], 1993 (Box 8, Folder 668)
  - Woodbridge Hall: President Levin and student [mm 91], 1994 March 28 (Box 8, Folder 669)
  - Woodcarver (John Nash) [mm 465.1], 1998 October (Box 8, Folder 670)
  - Woolsey Hall: President's Room Carpet Installation [mm 136], 1993 April 27 (Box 8, Folder 671)
  - World Game [mm 268], 1995 January 27 (Box 8, Folder 672)
  - Wright Nuclear Structure Lab: Group shot in lab [mm 118], 1993 March 25 (Box 8, Folder 673)
  - Yale Art Gallery: Conservators working on sculpture, Circa 1990s (Box 8, Folder 674)
  - Yale Art Gallery: "Stacks" Installation (R. Serra), Circa 1990s (Box 8, Folder 675)
  - Yale Art Gallery/New Haven: Students with education staff, Circa 1990s (Box 8, Folder 676)
  - Yale Book Store and Old Campus, Circa 1990s (Box 8, Folder 677)
  - Yale Bowl -- Interior and Exterior [mm 272], 1994 November (Box 8, Folder 678)
  - Yale Bowl: Scorekeepers [mm 54], 1993 September (Box 8, Folder 679)
  - Yale Campaign [mm 474], 1997 (Box 8, Folder 680)
  - Yale Club Greater New Haven Scholars [mm 105], 1993 (Box 8, Folder 681)
  - Yale Club -- New Haven Scholars [mm 150], 1994 (Box 8, Folder 682)
  - Yale Club Scholars [mm 305], 1995 May 15 (Box 8, Folder 683)
  - Yale Club of New Haven [mm], 1998 (Box 8, Folder 684)
  - Yale Daily News [mm 391], 1996 August 23 (Box 8, Folder 685)
  - Yale Drama Students [mm 221], 1994 July (Box 8, Folder 686)
  - Yale Dramat Theater: Summer [mm 213], 1994 July 8 (Box 8, Folder 687)
  - Yale Easter Egg [mm 517], 1998 March 23 (Box 8, Folder 688)
  - Yale Field -- Renovations [mm 78], 1994 February (Box 8, Folder 689)
  - YPI: Yale Psychiatric Institute, Circa 1990s (Box 8, Folder 690)
  - Yale Health Plan (YHP) Pharmacy: Ribbon cutting [mm 57], 1993 November 3 (Box 8, Folder 691)
  - Yale Police (former Chief- Alan Guyet), Circa 1990s (Box 8, Folder 692)
  - YHP -- Students in front [mm 47], 1993 (Box 8, Folder 693)
  - Yale Hillel: Shots for brochure [mm 58], 1993 December 6 (Box 8, Folder 694)
  - Yale Mainland -- Taiwanese Society: Dennis Xu and Thomas Wu [mm 132], 1992 October 27 (Box 8, Folder 695)
  - Yale Medal [mm 59], 1993 November 30 (Box 8, Folder 696)
  - Yale Medicine [mm 24], 1992 August 5 (Box 8, Folder 697)
  - Yale Opera (Promo) [mm 401], 1998 November 14 (Box 8, Folder 698)
  - Yale Opera Students [mm 250], 1995 November 17 (Box 8, Folder 699)
  - Yale Philharmonic [mm 407], 1997 December 4 (Box 8, Folder 700)
  - Yale Police Substation [mm 201], 1994 July 19 (Box 8, Folder 701)
  - Yale Police -- Mountain Bike Patrol [mm 304], 1995 March 13 (Box 8, Folder 702)
  - Yale Rep: "The Colored Museum" [mm 139], 1992 November 10 (Box 8, Folder 703)
  - Yale Rep: Exhibition "The Colored Museum" [mm 119], 1992 December 8 (Box 8, Folder 704)
  - Yale Science and Engineering Association Inc. [jb 125], 1993 April 26 (Box 8, Folder 705)
  - Yale Station Ribbon Cutting [mm 67], 1993 December 9 (Box 8, Folder 706)
  - Yale Symphony Orchestra [mm 468], 1997 September 23 (Box 8, Folder 707)
  - Yale Undergraduate Admissions [mm 215], 1993 December 3 (Box 8, Folder 708)
  - Yale University Art Gallery (YUAG): Art Space Display [mm 138], 1992 November 2 (Box 8, Folder 709)
  - Yale Press -- Book Donation [mm 263], 1994 November 8 (Box 8, Folder 710)
  - Yale University Press dedication of new wing [mm 69], 1993 November 16 (Box 8, Folder 711)
  - Youth Day
    - [mm 297], 1995 April 8 (Box 8, Folder 712)
    - [mm 416], 1996 April (Box 8, Folder 713)
  - Jerry Brown at Calhoun, 1999 October (Box 8, Folder 714)
  - Teaching at Yale, 1998 August 31 (Box 8, Folder 715)
  - Yale University Buildings
    - Accelerator lab, Circa 1990s (Box 8, Folder 716)
    - Metal Works (Samuel Yellin), Circa 1990s (Box 8, Folder 717)
    - Pamphlets, Circa 1990s (Box 8, Folder 718)
    - Art and Architecture, Circa 1990s (Box 8, Folder 719)
    - Battell Chapel, Circa 1990s (Box 8, Folder 720)
    - Bass Center, Circa 1990s (Box 9, Folder 721 - 723)
    - Beinecke Library, Circa 1990s (Box 9, Folder 724)
    - Boyer Center, Circa 1990s (Box 9, Folder 725 - 727)
    - Calhoun College courtyard, Circa 1990s (Box 9, Folder 728)
    - Connecticut Hall exterior and rooftop, Circa 1990s (Box 9, Folder 729)
    - University Commons Interior, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 730)
    - Davenport College, Circa 1990s (Box 9, Folder 731)
    - Ezra Stiles College, Circa 1990s (Box 9, Folder 732)
    - Woodbridge Hall, Circa 1990s (Box 9, Folder 733)
    - Hall of Graduate Studies exterior and rooftop, Circa 1990s (Box 9, Folder 734)
    - Harkness Tower, Circa 1990s (Box 9, Folder 735 - 736)
    - William L. Harkness Hall (WLH) exterior, Circa 1990s (Box 9, Folder 737)
    - Hewitt Quadrangle, Circa 1990s (Box 9, Folder 738)
    - lngalls Rink, Circa 1990s (Box 9, Folder 739)
    - Jonathan Edwards College, Circa 1990s (Box 9, Folder 740)
    - Kline Biology Tower (KBT) exterior, Circa 1990s (Box 9, Folder 741)
    - Law School, Circa 1990s (Box 9, Folder 742)
    - Lawrence Hall, Circa 1990s (Box 9, Folder 743)
    - Mason Laboratory, Circa 1990s (Box 9, Folder 744)
    - Osborn Memorial Laboratories (OML), Circa 1990s (Box 9, Folder 745)
    - Payne Whitney Gymnasium, Circa 1990s (Box 9, Folder 746)
    - Peabody Museum, Circa 1990s (Box 9, Folder 747)
    - Silliman Dining Hall [mm 441], 1996 June (Box 9, Folder 748)
    - School of Management (SOM), Circa 1990s (Box 9, Folder 749)
    - Sprague Hall, Circa 1990s (Box 9, Folder 750)
    - Sterling Chemistry Buildig [H. Shapiro], 2001 September (Box 9, Folder 751)
    - Sterling Chemistry Laboratory, Circa 1990s (Box 9, Folder 752)
    - Sterling Hall of Medicine (SHM), Circa 1990s (Box 9, Folder 753)
    - Sterling Memorial Library, Circa 1990s (Box 9, Folder 754 - 755)
    - Sudler Hall, Circa 1990s (Box 9, Folder 756)
    - Watson Hall, Circa 1990s (Box 9, Folder 757)
    - Whitney / Grove [mm 479], 1997 October 6 (Box 9, Folder 758)
    - Woolsey Hall, Circa 1990s (Box 9, Folder 759)
  - Miscellaneous University Photos
    - Admissions
      - Undergraduate, 1988 September (Box 9, Folder 760)
      - Affirmative Action YCll, 1989 July (Box 9, Folder 761)
      - Affirmative Action, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 762)
      - Yale Office of Undergraduate Admissions, 1989 September (Box 9, Folder 763)
      - Undergraduate Science Brochures
        - Recruitment, Circa 1990s (Box 9, Folder 764)
        - Physics, 1986 -1987 (Box 9, Folder 765 - 766)
    - AIDS-Busters Program (New Haven): Kaveh Khoshnood, Yale graduate student, 1991 April (Box 9, Folder 767)
    - AIDS Project New Haven
      - Volunteer opportunities: caring cuisine, 1991 February (Box 9, Folder 768)
      - Buddy program (James Gibbons and James Weiss), 1991 March (Box 9, Folder 769)
    - AIDS Task Force: Dr. Alvin Novick, 1987 March (Box 9, Folder 770)
    - AIDS Research on women: Rodin and Ickovics, 1991 December (Box 9, Folder 771)
    - Arms of Yale University, Circa 1990s (Box 9, Folder 772)
    - Bands of Yale University, Circa 1990s (Box 9, Folder 773)
    - Beinecke Rare Book Library
      - Information, Circa 1990s (Box 9, Folder 774)
      - General, Circa 1990s (Box 9, Folder 775)
      - General collection (modern), Circa 1990s (Box 9, Folder 776)
      - Stephen Emmel holding papyrus, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 777)
      - Medieval manuscript (Robert G. Babcock), 1987 November (Box 9, Folder 778)
      - Gutenberg Bible, Circa 1990s (Box 9, Folder 779)
    - Campus Overview, 2001 June (Box 10, Folder 780)
    - China: Beijing Tienanman Square student uprising press conference at Yale, 1989 September 12 (Box 10, Folder 781)
    - Chinese Students (Ma, Wang and Cong), 1986 February (Box 10, Folder 782)
    - Christmas
      - 1977-1982 (Box 10, Folder 783)
      - New Haven Green, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 784)
      - Museum Shop, Yale Center for British Art, 1988 December (Box 10, Folder 785)
      - New Haven, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 786)
    - Yale Name -Use of, Circa 1990s (Box 10, Folder 787)
    - Community Relations: New Haven-"Focus"-Student Volunteer Program, 1991-1992 (Box 10, Folder 788 - 789)
    - Traditions-Yale (lvy, Class day pipes, Handkerchief waving, Banners, Flags), Circa 1990s (Box 10, Folder 790)
    - Alcohol-Drug Education: Radio play award-Karl Gajdusek '90, 1988 February (Box 10, Folder 791)
    - Co-education: 20th anniversary poster unveiling, 1989 October (Box 10, Folder 792)
    - Coeducation, Circa 1990s (Box 10, Folder 793)
    - Engineering: Microzoom Microscope (Wentworth Labs), Circa 1990s (Box 10, Folder 794)
    - Fellowships: Academic Mentorship Program in the Sciences and Bouchet, 1991 June (Box 10, Folder 795)
    - Type house -- Memos, Circa 1990s (Box 10, Folder 796)
    - Hewitt Quadrangle, 2001 April (Box 10, Folder 797)
    - Gay Rights: Press conference, Schmidt and Wellington, 1989 November (Box 10, Folder 798)
    - Graduate School -- Wilbur Cross Medal, Circa 1990s (Box 10, Folder 799)
    - Grant, Ulysses S. Foundation, Circa 1990s (Box 10, Folder 800)
    - Howland Prize: Henry Elias Howland Memorial Prize--The Howland Medal, Circa 1990s (Box 10, Folder 801)
    - Humanities: Sid Bass Gift -- Faculty -- Classrooms, 1990 October (Box 10, Folder 802)
    - Human Resources: Long-Service Awards, 1991-1993 (Box 10, Folder 803 - 805)
    - Instructional Technology Group (AV, Film, Compuuting, Language Lab), 1992 February (Box 10, Folder 806)
    - International and Area Studies: Henry R. Luce International Center, 1991 January (Box 10, Folder 807)
    - New Haven Green, Circa 1990s (Box 10, Folder 808 - 809)
    - New Haven, Circa 1990s (Box 10, Folder 810)
    - Recycling
      - Newhallville, Inc., 1990 November (Box 10, Folder 811)
      - Recyclo -- weekly lottery, 1990 September (Box 10, Folder 812)
    - New Haven
      - Restaurant: Robert Henry's -- Slides, 1987 May (Box 10, Folder 813)
      - Phil's Barber Shops, Circa 1990s (Box 10, Folder 814)
      - Shubert Theatre, Circa 1990s (Box 10, Folder 815)
      - Green -- renovations, 1990 September (Box 10, Folder 816)
      - Celebration 343 Years, 1981 April 24-26 (Box 10, Folder 817)
      - At night, Circa 1990s (Box 10, Folder 818)
      - Canal Line, Circa 1990s (Box 10, Folder 819)
      - Methodist Church Fire, 1987 September (Box 10, Folder 820)
      - Yale's Annual Salute to New Haven In honor of: Virgil C. Dechant, Knights of Columbus, 1982 September 16 (Box 10, Folder 821)
      - Science Park Prospect Inn, Circa 1990s (Box 10, Folder 822)
      - Whitney Avenue, Circa 1990s (Box 10, Folder 823)
      - Union Station, Circa 1990s (Box 10, Folder 824)
    - Physics: ESTU (Extended Stretched TransUranium) Nuclear Accelerator
      - Dedication and Symposium, 1987 August (Box 10, Folder 825)
      - Pre-dedication, 1987 July (Box 10, Folder 826)
    - Recycling
      - Bins Being Delivered to Dean Ezra Laderman (Music School), 1987 August (Box 10, Folder 827)
    - Presidency of Yale: Symbols of Office
      - The University Mace, 1991 April (Box 10, Folder 829)
      - The President's Collar
        - New Collar, 1982 May (Box 10, Folder 830)
        - "Original" 1905 Collar, Circa 1980s (Box 10, Folder 831)
      - Symbols, Circa 1980s (Box 10, Folder 832)
    - Recycling, 1990 January (Box 10, Folder 833)
    - Ribbon cutting (B. Schmidt, A. E. Braun, Jr., Cyril May), 1990 March (Box 10, Folder 828)
    - Scenics, 1991, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 834 - 835)
    - Scenics
      - Wlndows, Circa 1990s (Box 10, Folder 837 - 838)
      - Outdoor Sculpture, Circa 1990s (Box 10, Folder 839)
    - Sterling Memorial Library
      - Color Slides (Paul Penders), 1988 May (Box 10, Folder 840)
      - "Buttress", 1991 June (Box 10, Folder 841)
      - Color slides/prints, Circa 1990s (Box 11, Folder 842)
      - Archives and Manuscripts, Circa 1990s (Box 11, Folder 843)
      - Interiors Reading Room, 1990 March (Box 11, Folder 844)
      - Libraries supplement -- YWBand, 1989 October (Box 11, Folder 845)
      - Yale University Libraries, 1992 January (Box 11, Folder 846)
      - Main Reference Room -- C.V. Starr Reference Center, 1992 January (Box 11, Folder 847)
    - Students: Activities Old Campus: Juggling, Golf, etc., 1988 (Box 10, Folder 836)
    - Beinecke Library: Josephine Baker Collection, Circa 1990s (Box 11, Folder 848)
    - Scenics, Circa 1990s (Box 11, Folder 849)
    - Buildings: Gateways: Noah Porter Gateway, Circa 1990s (Box 11, Folder 850)
    - Scenics
      - Stone Carvings
        - Christian Pain: Stonecutter, Circa 1990s (Box 11, Folder 851)
        - Harkness Tower, Circa 1990s (Box 11, Folder 852)
        - HGS, Berkeley, Branford, Nota Bene, Law School, etc., 1985-1991 (Box 11, Folder 853)
      - Snow Scenes, Circa 1990s (Box 11, Folder 854)
    - Security
      - YAM, Artlcle New Card System, 1992 February (Box 11, Folder 855)
      - Awareness Week, 1989 February (Box 11, Folder 856)
      - Yale Police Dept., Circa 1990s (Box 11, Folder 857)
      - Security Supplement, 1980 September (Box 11, Folder 858)
      - Emergency Phones Illumination, 1991 April (Box 11, Folder 859)
      - Yale Shuttle Bus, Circa 1990s (Box 11, Folder 860)
      - Student Escort "2-walk", 1992 January (Box 11, Folder 861)
    - South Africa
      - Divestment Project, 1986 April (Box 11, Folder 862)
      - Press conference, 1986 July (Box 11, Folder 863)
      - Apartheid Protest, The Wall, Talking it down, 1991 February (Box 11, Folder 864)
      - Panels, Circa 1990s (Box 11, Folder 865)
      - Apartheid Protest Shanties Fire, 1988 June (Box 11, Folder 866 - 867)
    - Sociology: Graduate School: Sociology, Chakerian Research Fund, 1990 April (Box 11, Folder 868)
    - Statues
      - Abraham Pierson, 1990 April (Box 11, Folder 869)
      - Benjamin Silliman, Circa 1990s (Box 11, Folder 870)
    - Student Activities: Theatre: "Hair", 1992 April (Box 11, Folder 871)
    - Students
      - Minority and In Dorm, 1986 April (Box 11, Folder 872)
      - Art Classes, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 873)
      - Music Groups, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 874)
      - Classrooms, 1990-1991 (Box 11, Folder 875 - 876)
    - Campus Tours, Circa 1990s (Box 11, Folder 877)
    - Tours of Yale, 1985 August (Box 11, Folder 878)
    - Tour: Guided -- Yale, 1987, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 879 - 880)
    - Union: Yale Local No.35
      - Federation of University Employees, Circa 1990s (Box 11, Folder 881)
      - Strike, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 882)
      - Trades Helper Program, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 883)
    - Unions: Local 34 and Local 35
      - Contract Agreement Press Conference, 1992 February (Box 11, Folder 884)
      - Trades Assistants Program, 1985 Summer (Box 11, Folder 885)
      - Contract Agreements, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 886)
    - Union: Perfect Attendance, Circa 1990s (Box 11, Folder 887)
    - Western Civilization: Lee M. Bass Gift, 1991 April (Box 11, Folder 888)
  - Commencement
    - 1990 (Box 11, Folder 889 - 896)
    - 1990 (Box 12, Folder 897 - 900)
    - 1991 (Box 12, Folder 901 - 907)
    - 1992 (Box 12, Folder 908 - 917)
    - 1993 (Box 12, Folder 918 - 923)
    - 1994 (Box 12, Folder 924 - 926)
    - 1994 (Box 13, Folder 927 - 929)
    - 1995 (Box 13, Folder 930 - 934)
    - 1996 (Box 13, Folder 935 - 937)
    - 1997 (Box 13, Folder 938 - 943)
    - 1998 (Box 13, Folder 944 - 949)
    - 1999 (Box 13, Folder 950 - 951)
    - 2001 (Box 13, Folder 952)
    - 2002 (Box 13, Folder 953)
    - 2003 (Box 13, Folder 954)
    - BAC, Circa 2001 (Box 13, Folder 955)
    - REL Reception, Circa 2001 (Box 13, Folder 956)